Finding Aid for the Preston Sturges Papers LSC.1114
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Correspondence
  - Howard, William K., 7 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 32)
  - Hoy - Hz., 11 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 33)
  - Hoy - Hz., 16 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 34)
  - Hubert, René., 1 piece. (Box 72, Folder 35)
  - Hughes, Howard., 15 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 36)
  - Hughes, Rupert., 13 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 37)
  - Hughes Productions., 3 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 38)
  - Hughes Tool Company., 1 piece. (Box 72, Folder 39)
  - Hunt, Martita., 1 piece. (Box 72, Folder 40)
  - Hull, Henry., 1 piece. (Box 72, Folder 41)
  - Hull, Josephine., 2 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 42)
  - Hutton, Marjorie., 6 pieces. (Box 72, Folder 43)
  - I., 10 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - I., 10 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - I., 9 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Ihnen, Wiard., 2 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Iturbi, Josh., 8 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Ja., 10 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Ja., 12 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Ja., 10 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Jacquet, H. Maurice., 2 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - James, Daniel L., 9 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - James, Daniel L., 14 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Je - Jz., 10 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Je - Jz., 10 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Je - Jz., 10 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Je - Jz., 16 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - John, Alice., 2 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Johnston, Alva., 16 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Jones, Paul., 1 piece. (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Jorgenson, Lawrence., 10 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Jorgenson, Lawrence., 6 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Joseph, Rudolph., 6 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Judell, Maxson., 7 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Juergens, O.D., 7 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - K - Ka., 11 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - K - Ka., 11 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - K - Ka., 12 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - K - Ka., 10 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Kamins, Bernard F., 4 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Karp, Joseph., 1 piece. (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - Katz, Sam., 4 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Ke., 10 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - Ke., 10 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 32)
  - Ke., 10 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 33)
  - Ke., 18 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 34)
  - Kent, Atwater., 4 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 35)
  - Kh - K1., 10 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 36)
  - Kh - K1., 10 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 37)
  - Kh - K1., 11 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 38)
  - Kimbrough, Emily., 11 pieces. (Box 73, Folder 39)
  - Kl - Kn, 13 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Kl - Kn., 8 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Ko., 10 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Ko., 11 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Ko., 11 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Kohner, Paul., 12 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Kohner, Paul, 10 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Kohner, Paul., 14 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Kr - Kz., 10 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Kr - Kz., 15 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Kurnitz, Harry., 1 piece. (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - L - La., 12 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - L - La., 12 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - L - La., 13 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - L - La., 12 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - L - La., 14 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - La Cava, Gregory., 1 piece. (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Lachman, Harry., 1 piece. (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Laemmle, Ernst., 15 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Laemmle family (Carl, Carol & Walter)., 9 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Lake, Veronica., 1 piece. (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Lasky, Jesse L., 10 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Lasky, Jesse L., 10 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Lasky, Jesse L., 14 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Lawrence, Gertrude., 1 piece. (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - Le., 11 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - Le., 10 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - Le., 11 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - Le., 10 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 29)
  - Le., 11 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 30)
  - Le., 11 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 31)
  - Le., 15 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 32)
  - Le Baron, William., 6 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 33)
  - Le Borg, Reginald., 1 piece. (Box 74, Folder 34)
  - Leisin, J. Mitchell., 4 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 35)
  - Lek, Nico., 9 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 36)
  - Le Marchand, J., 6 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 37)
  - Le Roy, Mervyn., 1 piece. (Box 74, Folder 38)
  - Lesser, Sol., 3 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 39)
  - Le Veque, Edward., 5 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 40)
  - Levinson, Leonard L., 6 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 41)
  - Lewin, Albert., 2 pieces. (Box 74, Folder 42)
  - Li - Lo., 11 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Li - Lo., 11 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Li - Lo., 10 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Li - Lo., 10 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Li - Lo., 11 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Li - Lo., 10 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Li - Lo., 16 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Lieurance, Thurlow., 1 piece. (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Liveright, Horace. Publisher., 4 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Lloyd, Frank., 2 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Lloyd, Harold., 9 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Lloyds Register of American Yachts., 14 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Long, Dwight., 12 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Long, Dwight., 15 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Long, Robert W., 10 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Long, Robert W., 12 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Long, Robert W., 11 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Look Magazine., 12 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Lopes, Don., 2 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Lorentz, Pare., 5 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Loring, Paule., ca. 1948.; 10 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Loring, Paule., ca. 1948.; 12 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Loring, Paule., ca. 1948.; 10 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Loring, Paule., ca. 1948.; 12 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Loring, Paule., ca. 1948.; 10 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Loring, Paule., ca. 1948.; 12 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Loring, Paule., ca. 1948.; 11 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Loring, Paule., ca. 1948.; 19 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Los Angeles., 10 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Los Angeles., 14 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Los Angeles County and City., 8 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Love, Sidney C., 10 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Love, Sidney C., 10 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - Love, Sidney C., 13 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 34)
  - Love, Sidney C., 10 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 35)
  - Love, Sidney C., 11 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 36)
  - Love, Sidney C., 12 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 37)
  - Love, Sidney C., 11 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 38)
  - Love, Sidney C., 11 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 39)
  - Lu - Lz., 12 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 40)
  - Lu - Lz., 18 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 41)
  - Lubitsch, Ernst., 5 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 42)
  - Luce, Clare Booth., 1 piece. (Box 75, Folder 43)
  - Luce, Henry R., 5 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 44)
  - Lytton, Madeleine., 14 pieces. (Box 75, Folder 45)
  - Ma., 12 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Ma., 10 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Ma., 12 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Ma., 10 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Ma., 10 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Ma., 12 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Ma., 11 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Ma., 13 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Ma., 13 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Ma., 18 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Mc., 10 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Mc., 11 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Mc., 12 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Mc., 14 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Mc., 11 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Mc., 9 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - McConnell, Keith., 12 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - McConnell, Keith., 7 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - McCormick, Fowler., 3 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - McCrea, Joel., 2 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Macgowan, Kenneth., 6 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - MacKenna, Kenneth., 2 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Mann, Christopher., 5 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Mann, Hank., 1 piece. (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Manning, Bruce., 1 piece. (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Mannix, Edgar J., 2 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - March, Fredric., 1 piece. (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - Marsh, Mae., 2 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - Marshall, Herbert., 1 piece. (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - Mason, James & Pamela., 7 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - Mayer, Louis., 1 piece. (Box 76, Folder 31)
  - Mayo, Eddie., 3 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 32)
  - Me - Mi., 13 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 33)
  - Me - Mi., 12 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 34)
  - Me - Mi., 10 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 35)
  - Me - Mi., 11 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 36)
  - Me - Mi., 12 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 37)
  - Me - Mi., 10 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 38)
  - Me - Mi., 12 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 39)
  - Me - Mi., 12 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 40)
  - Me - Mi., 9 pieces. (Box 76, Folder 41)
  - Menjou, Adolphe., 1 piece. (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Merlino, Maxine., 12 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Merlino, Maxine., 19 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Metro Goldwyn Mayer., 5 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Meyer, Torben., 13 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Meyer, Torben., 19 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Meyer, Torben., 10 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Meyer, Torben., 12 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Meyer, Torben., 11 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Mintz, Sam., 8 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Moa - Moo., 13 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Moa - Moo., 17 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Moldavan, Andre., 11 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Moore, Colleen., 3 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Mop - Moz., 11 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Mop - Moz., 10 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Mop - Moz., 11 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Mop - Moz., 10 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Moracchine, Tules., 15 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Moran, Frank., 7 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Morehouse, Ward., 9 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Morris, Chester., 1 piece. (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Morris, Gouverneur., 12 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Morros, Boris., 2 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Mu - Mz., 11 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Mu - Mz., 16 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Mu - Mz., 15 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Museum - City of New York., 10 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Museum - City of New York., 8 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - N - Ne., 12 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 30)
  - N - Ne., 10 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 31)
  - N - Ne., 10 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 32)
  - N - Ne., 11 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 33)
  - N - Ne., 12 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 34)
  - N - Ne., 11 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 35)
  - Nagle, Edward., 12 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 36)
  - Nagle, Edward., 8 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 37)
  - Nagle, Frederick., 5 pieces. (Box 77, Folder 38)
  - Nagle, Helen (mother)., 1954.; 11 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Nagle, Helen (mother)., 1954.; 10 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Nagle, Helen (mother)., 1955.; 12 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Nagle, Helen (mother)., 1955.; 10 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Nagle, Helen (mother)., 1955.; 10 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Nagle, Helen (mother)., 1956.; 14 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Nagle, Helen (mother)., 1956.; 12 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Nagle, Helen (mother)., 1956.; 7 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Nagle, Helen (mother). &, 1956 n.d.; 9 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Nagle,.Mary., 2 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - NBC., 4 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - New York State., 9 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Newman, Alfred., 4 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Newton, Robert., 2 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Ni - Nz., 10 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Ni - Nz., 12 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Ni - Nz., 15 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Nichols, Dudley., 3 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - 0., 10 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - 0., 12 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - 0., 10 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - 0., 10 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - 0., 18 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - OGASCO., 7 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - O'Brien, Edmond., 2 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - O'Connell, Arthur & Janet., 3 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Odets, Clifford., 1 piece. (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Olsen., Edwin., 14 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Ophuls, Max., 9 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - Oriel, J.P., 11 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - Orsatti Agency., 12 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - Orsatti Agency., 12 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - Orsatti Agency., 11 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 33)
  - Orsatti Agency., 10 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 34)
  - Orsatti Agency., 12 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 35)
  - Orsatti Agency., 14 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 36)
  - Orsatti Agency., 14 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 37)
  - Orsatti Agency., 11 pieces. (Box 78, Folder 38)
  - Pa., 10 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Pa., 10 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Pa., 22 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Pa., 13 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Pa., 10 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Pa., 14 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Pa., 10 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Pa., 16 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Pagnol, Marcel., 15 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Paramore, Edward Jr., 2 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Parker, John., 8 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Parsons, Louella., 1 piece. (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Palmer, Lilli., 1 piece. (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Paramount Pictures Incorporated., n.d.-1940.; 11 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Paramount Pictures Incorporated., n.d.-1940.; 10 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Paramount Pictures Incorporated., n.d.-1940.; 12 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Paramount Pictures Incorporated., n.d.-1940.; 10 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Paramount Pictures Incorporated., n.d.-1940.; 10 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Paramount Pictures Incorporated., n.d.-1940.; 13 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Paramount Pictures Incorporated., 1941-1953.; 11 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Paramount Pictures Incorporated., 1941-1953.; 12 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Paramount Pictures Incorporated., 1941-1953.; 11 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Paramount Pictures Incorporated., 1941-1953.; 10 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Paramount Pictures Incorporated., 1941-1953.; 15 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Paramount Pictures Incorporated., 1941-1953.; 19 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Pe - Pl., 10 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - Pe - Pl., 11 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Pe - Pl., 10 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Pe - Pl., 12 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - Pe - Pl., 11 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - Pe - Pl., 10 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - Pe - Pl., 10 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - Pearson, Temple Duncan., 7 pieces. (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - Pelham, David M., 2 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Pemberton, Brock., 15 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Pemberton, Murdoch., 1 piece. (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Perch, H.L., 2 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Perry, Antoinette., 3 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Perry, Elaine., 3 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art., 11 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Pichel, Irving., 2 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Pickford, Mary., 7 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Pillet, Alexis., 10 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Planer, Franz., 2 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - The Players, New York., 25 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Po - Pz., 14 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Po - Pz., 11 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Po - Pz., 12 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Po - Pz., 10 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Po - Pz., 10 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Po - Pz., 13 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Po - Pz., 18 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Porter, Cole., 1 piece. (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Q., 4 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Ra - Ri., 11 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Ra - Ri., 11 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Ra - Ri., 11 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Ra - Ri., 10 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Ra - Ri., 10 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - Ra - Ri., 10 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - Ra - Ri., 10 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - Ra - Ri., 11 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - Ra - Ri., 12 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - Raines, Ella., 2 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Ramsden, Frances., 19 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - Ramsden, Frances., 10 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - Ramsden, Frances., 10 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 34)
  - Ramsden, Frances., 10 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 35)
  - Ramsden, Frances., 12 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 36)
  - Ramsden, Frances., 12 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 37)
  - Ramsden, Frances., 9 pieces. (Box 80, Folder 38)
  - Ratoff, Gregory., 4 pieces. (Box 81, Folder l)
  - Reade, Walter Jr., 3 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Reisner, Bika de., 11 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Reisner, Bika de., 10 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Reisner, Bika de., 9 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Remarque, Erich Marie., 2 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Renavent, George., 3 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Riverside Yacht Club, Connecticut., 10 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Riverside Yacht Club, Connecticut., 10 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Riverside Yacht Club, Connecticut., 10 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Riverside Yacht Club, Connecticut., 8 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Ro - Rz., 10 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Ro - Rz., 13 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Ro - Rz., 10 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Ro - Rz., 11 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Ro - Rz., 12 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Ro - Rz., 10 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - Ro - Rz., 10 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Ro - Rz., 10 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - Ro - Rz., 11 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Ro - Rz., 11 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Roehn, Franz F., 6 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - Roenheld, Heinz., 7 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - Rogers, Bogart., 12 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - Rose, Billy., 3 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - Ross, Harold W. (The New Yorker)., 5 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - Rubinstein, Arthur., 1 piece. (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - Sa., 11 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 28)
  - Sa., 10 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 29)
  - Sa., 12 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 30)
  - Sa., 15 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 31)
  - Sa., 10 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 32)
  - Sa., 11 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 33)
  - Sa., 9 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 34)
  - Sainte Colombe, Paul de., 13 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 35)
  - Sc., 12 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 36)
  - Sc., 10 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 37)
  - Sc., 12 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 38)
  - Sc., 15 pieces. (Box 81, Folder 39)
  - Schaetel, Irving., 1 piece. (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Schroeder, Arnold., 12 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Schroeder, Arnold., 16 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Schulberg, Benjamin., 8 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Screen Actors Guild., 13 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Screen Actors Guild., 10 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Screen Actors Guild., 11 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Screen Actors Guild., 21 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Scully, Frank., 5 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Se., 10 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Se., 11 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Se., 18 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Selwyn, Edgar., 2 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Selznick, David 0., 2 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Serlin, Oscar., 13 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Sequence magazine., 10 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Sh., 11 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Sh., 10 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Sh., 10 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Sh., 10 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Sh., 14 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Si., 10 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Si., 10 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Si., 12 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Siegel, Sot., 3 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Simon & Schuster Incorporated., 2 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Simonson, Lee., 2 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Singer, Cecil & Laura., 7 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - Singer, Paris & Jean., 11 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - Singer, Paris & Jean., 10 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Singer, Paris & Jean., 8 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Sk., 11 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - Skouras, Spyros., 3 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 33)
  - Sl., 11 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 34)
  - Slaughter, Bessie., 8 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 35)
  - Sm - Sr., 10 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 36)
  - Sm - Sr., 10 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 37)
  - Sm -Sr., 12 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 38)
  - Sm - Sr., 12 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 39)
  - Sm - Sr., 11 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 40)
  - Sm - Sr., 18 pieces. (Box 82, Folder 41)
  - Songs. (Box 82, Folder 42)
  - Snyder, Ted & Marie., 10 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Somers, Anne., 5 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Soskin, Paul., 2 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Spencer, Howland., 14 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Sta., 10 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Sta., 10 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Sta., 10 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Stanwyck, Barbara., 2 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Ste., 11 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Ste., 15 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Ste., 12 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Ste., 14 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Stern, Seymour., 12 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Stern, Seymour., 10 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Stern, Seymour., 10 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Stern, Seymour., 10 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Stern, Seymour., 10 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Stewart, William Lyman Jr., 5 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 18)
  - Sti - Stu., 10 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 19)
  - Sti - Stu., 13 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 20)
  - Sti - Stu., 12 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 21)
  - Sti - Stu., 10 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 22)
  - Sti - Stu., 11 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 23)
  - Sti - Stu., 13 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 24)
  - Stokowski, Leopold., 1 piece. (Box 83, Folder 25)
  - Su - Sz., 12 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 26)
  - Su - Sz., 8 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 27)
  - Sullavan, Margaret., 2 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 28)
  - Swanson, Gloria., 2 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 29)
  - Sylvia, Gabrielle., 6 pieces. (Box 83, Folder 30)
  - Sturges, Sandy. (Anne M. Nagle)., 1953; 9 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Sturges, Sandy -, 1954.; 1 piece. (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1955.; 2 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1956.; 1 piece. (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1957.; 11 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1957.; 14 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1957.; 13 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1957.; 11 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1957.; 12 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1957.; 12 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1957.; 11 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1957.; 16 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1958.; 11 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1958.; 12 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1958.; 11 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1958.; 13 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1958.; 10 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1958.; 11 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1958.; 14 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1959.; 11 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1959.; 11 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Sturges, Sandy., 1959.; 13 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Sturges, Charles., 12 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - Sturges, Charles., 12 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 24)
  - Sturges, Charles., 12 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 25)
  - Sturges, Frank & Lillian., 11 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 26)
  - Sturges, Frank & Lillian., 17 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 27)
  - Sturges, George., 10 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 28)
  - Sturges, Hollister & family., 6 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 29)
  - Sturges, Jannette L., 4 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 30)
  - Sturges, Lee & Mary., 10 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 31)
  - Sturges, Lee & Mary., 11 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 32)
  - Sturges, Louise., 11 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 33)
  - Sturges, Louise., 14 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 34)
  - Sturges, Louise., 10 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 35)
  - Sturges, Louise., 11 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 36)
  - Sturges, Louise., 15 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 37)
  - Sturges, Louise., 17 pieces. (Box 84, Folder 38)